Robert Linville

Evansville, IN 47712 rtlinville2214@gmail.com 270-875-1504

Looking for a career not a job. Tired of the driving scene. Would like to return to manufacturing. Looking at my resume does not justify my experience in manufacturing over the time since I began working several years ago. Several years of forklift experience working in food grade plants in a warehouse setting and quality control in food grade.

I have the experience that makes me a top candidate that you are looking for.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Driver Fuel Tech

Savage Fueling Services - Evansville, IN September 2018 to Present

Fuel trains

Driver

Beelman Trucking
April 2018 to September 2018

- Perform pre-trip inspections
- Perform post-trip inspections
- · Assist other drivers as needed
- Haul and deliver coal and rock
- Track daily production

Team Lead/Driver

Berry Global

July 2013 to March 2018

- Supervision of 6 drivers
- Conduct Safety Meetings and pre shift meetings
- Delegate delivery of finished product
- Drive a semi pulling trailers with finished product to off-site storage facility
- Quality assurance using Density, impact, multiple measurement accuracy (calipar), multiple leakage testing, microscope testing. All using the Keyance system. Recording all information into Excel.
- Drive a fork truck loading and unloading trucks
- Check the incoming/outgoing freight with BOL/shipping POD/freight bill
- Organizing stock
- Pulling orders, packing, wrapping, prep label and paperwork for shipping
- Conduct monthly and weekly inventory review
- Daily pre-shift and post shift safety checks
- Keep production areas running properly with correct material staged and return/move product to warehouse for storage

Contract Miner

David Stanley

October 2012 to July 2013

- Build brattices and cribs, work reclaim and set timbers by belt lines, intakes and returns
- Rock dusted and shoveled the belt lines
- Trained on how to safely operate the low trac, man trip, and bus
- Follow all safety protocols set forth by the mine, state and federal mining offices

Education

General Studies

Madisonville Community College - Madisonville, KY 2008 to 2011

High School Diploma

Dawson Springs High School - Dawson Springs, KY 1996

Skills

MICROSOFT OFFICE, MS OFFICE, TYPING, Forklift, Warehousing

Additional Information

Special Skills

- Basic computer knowledge and typing skills
- Microsoft Office
- Safety committee member at Berry Global
- Fork Truck Operator